In September, a local woman's body was discovered washed up on the riverbank.
Police had originally suspected the death to be a suicide.
However, several recent discoveries are beginning to paint this case in a new light.
Authorities now suspect foul play to be involved in her passing.
Whatever the truth is, we'd like to encourage our female listeners to stay aware of your surroundings
and mind both your physical and mental health.
Yes, we know this situation has many of our listeners wary.
But we thank you for your continued support
and know that together, we will overcome this hardship.
Uh,陆光?
Uh, who is this?
Huh?
I have no idea.
I was just about to ask you why you have a stalker.
I mean no harm.
Chen Xiao, I'm an architect.
I read online about people who can enter photos.
Oh!
Well, that changes everything!
Sorry he's rude.
So, uh, why were you watching me run?
Because of the rumors.
Some say that you're some kind of fairy.
Others say you're an old witch.
Hold on!
Did you say old?
I didn't want to get conned, so I figured I'd observe you first.
So would you be willing to help?
I'm begging you.
Let's restart.
Drop the fairy thing.
Call me Xiao Xiao.
Xiao Xiao?
No, no, no.
Listen, it's Xiao Xiao.
It didn't take too long to realize
Something has changed in the back of my mind
Your eyes
There ain't nowhere left to hide behind
Time no longer flew like it was
When the flash froze everything before
Without you
I don't know if I could take this road
And I'm about to lose my mind
Every minute that I die back in time
Every single day exists this rewinds
Some physical pain in this eye drive
All night
All the heartaches and the smiles never faded
I know you'll be by my side when we make it
Come back from the times
Back in time
Die back in time
Huh, isn't this a picture I developed a few days ago?
Our witch really keeps us busy.
What's the deal?
Our client was a benchwarmer on his team
And the school paper's photographer.
I took this picture before the last game
It was the most horrible day of my life
I failed a friend
Missed my first love
And got in an awful fight with my mom
Now
I live with regret
I need them all
To know what went unsaid
Well, what do you think?
Is that kind of thing allowed?
Hold up
Won't this mess up the timeline?
That's a no-no
Everything will be fine
Nothing will be affected
If you're sure
Let's go
All right
Bring the fire, boys
If we take this one
We'll be off to the county tourney
Yeah!
Hey, Chen
Watch the other team closely
If any of us gets hurt
You're on the court
We're counting on you
And make sure you stay warmed up
Right
You can be called in at any moment
We left out this year
I barely even call these guys a team
Just some losers in sad jerseys
Driving all this way was a waste
Right?
And what's with this crappy building?
It'll crumble any second now
No doubt
That's not such a joke
Lead us to victory!
Show these guys
Everybody's great to play Long Young
The game is the only thing
I doubt they'll put up much of a fight
I'm already bored
Can we start?
Hey, listen
Yes
Let's not forget
We need good pictures
That way, others might want to join us
Sure thing, Captain
All over it
I can barely see while wearing these dumb glasses
I should ditch them
You don't even play
Just sit back and relax
Long Young, Long Young
Dominate the ball!
Win for us all!
Woohoo!
Don't get down
It's early
Stay strong
Can't see anything
Don't get to play
This is driving me
This is driving me insane
Talk to the captain after the game
That'll be one person checked off
Try to stay out of trouble until then
Alright, pictures
That'll kill time
No flash
Turn it off
Crap
Offensive charging from Long Young
Hey, Lou
That's not good
Did I change the timeline?
Technically, but it won't last
Just keep at it
Things should straighten out
That's a relief
What?
I could barely see because their idiot teammate was using the flash
It's not my fault
Blame that guy
I'm sorry, Captain
I wasn't thinking
How's the knee?
Fine
Don't feel bad
He pulled that foul on purpose
Take my place
I'll get this knee taken care of while you're out there
You're our last hope
Do us proud
Hey, so, uh
Is this part of the plan?
Should I play or not?
You threw a wrench in things
I'm not positive how this game is supposed to play out now
But your team must lose
Right
I'll try my best
If this guy's your backup, you might as well call it
Moron
We're not done
Damn it
Defense, now!
No one's better on the court than me
No one
New guy
Want to join us?
Pass it back
Let's go
You look kind of worried
Keep an eye on this guy
Protect the ball
When the heck did he get so good?
Defense!
Heard!
Right!
Dude, you're channeling Kobe out there!
What the hell?
That was awesome!
Dang, man
Where'd you learn moves like those?
That was amazing
He must be practicing in secret
With you, we've got a good chance of winning this
Right, Cap, consider it done
Not so fast
They have to lose
We can't change the overall result
But you know, it takes an entire team to win
So let's all do our best, yeah?
Your mission isn't to show off during a basketball game
Reign it in
Yeah, I will
Hey, Captain
Take it easy
Come have a seat
Without him, your team's nothing
Which is why he still tried to pass to me
Oh yeah, the second half is my time to shine
How's my acting?
Is it obvious I'm bailing?
Hey, so what happened to our new ace's skills?
Guys!
Basketball's a team sport
You realize he's been deliberately attracting their attention
That created scoring opportunities for the rest of you
Wow, I get it
Come on, let's rally
That's right, we're a team
You said it
Nice pass
Wow, that was a beeline for my hands
Amazing
Dude, just keep playing like that and we'll try and keep up with you
Yeah, sure
What's going on?
It's just Unlock
No way he's that good
What more can I do?
Time out from Motor Factory
Longyang, Longyang, dominate the bomb!
Longyang, Longyang, win it for us all!
I want you to stay here
Uh-oh
Has he caught on?
Your body's shutting down
Too much exertion
Take a break
The school doc dropped by and wrapped me up
I'm good
Let's take it home
Can he really play with that limp?
What if he gets hurt worse?
He should play while he can
Because I doubt there'll be any more chances in the future
Our town doesn't have much going for it
School resources are limited
This gymnasium used to be a factory
The workers built it themselves back in the day
When the auto business went busted and closed
Students started using it for games
And the school allowed it
But
They plan to expand the campus soon
If we can show that we're serious and can win
Maybe they won't tear down the courts
The school's never had a basketball team before
There's no precedent
Then we'll set one
You have to let us try
In towns like this
The only real way to make a better life for yourself
Is through studying
The basketball dream is just a fairy tale
Nothing more
Nothing less
Please coach
I need to get back on the court
Did you hit your head?
You forget I'm just a chemistry teacher
Your kids need to get yourselves together
And be more rational
What does basketball mean to you anyway?
It's obvious to see you hold it dear
We make a nice game
I think
We'll make good partners in the future
You're so serious
It's just a game
Nope
You're wrong there
See, whenever I pass the ball to you
It means that I trust you
You get it?
Partnerships like that are a rare thing
Don't take them for granted
Just remember
You exist in the past right now
This isn't your life
I know
I've got to do whatever I can
To make up for his regrets
Nothing more
Nothing less
Get the rebound
Whoa
Captain
Coach, put me in
Don't
Yeah
Stay off
Time out from Motor Factory
Hey, are you okay?
It's too much
I can't stand on it
I promise, Captain
This won't be our last game on this court
Stop it
Don't forget your role
It's good
Here
It's like he's flying
Yes
Whoa
They're only up by three points
Still got a chance
Defense is vital now
Come on, let's go
Move it
That's a personal foul
From Long Yong
Whoops
Sorry, bro
Didn't mean to trash your glasses
Totally my bad
Sure
Come on
We don't want to get home too late
Long Yong, Long Yong
Dominate the ball
Win your first ball
Who the hell?
He shot a three-pointer?
Let's control the ball
And run down the clock
He pulled a bounce pass?
Just let it happen
You know it has to be this way
Give it up
Don't do this
Pass it
Stop him now
What does basketball mean to you anyway?
It's obvious to see you hold it dear
Huh
μέics
啊
I got lost in the street and I'm living in
Or maybe I should just quit overthinking
Yeah, I should really stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Stop stop thinking about it
Why your mind overclouded
脱离现实的梦境化为寂寞
始终的我需要怎样才能自保
So stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Why your mind overclouded
在这时间的风险停止思考
我明白多少烦恼都是勇然自扰
Yeah
Stop thinking about it
Why your mind overclouded
Yeah
Sí